{"entity_1": "Reebok", "entity_2": "Canton", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Reebok</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Canton</LOC> , <LOC>Massachusetts</LOC> , has awarded human rights grants to 60 activists from 35 countries since the program started in 1998 .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", Massachusetts", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Citigroup", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Citigroup</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>New York</LOC> , is selling the shares as part of its effort to repay $ 20 billion in federal bailout funds .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", is", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lufthansa", "entity_2": "Cologne", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Shares of <ORG>Lufthansa</ORG> , based in <LOC>Cologne</LOC> , were up 3.1 percent on the news , trading at euro12 .66 ( $ 17.07 ) in <LOC>Frankfurt</LOC> .", "bef_words": "Shares of", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", were", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Concentra", "entity_2": "Addison", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Privately held <ORG>Concentra</ORG> , based in <LOC>Addison</LOC> , <LOC>Texas</LOC> , delivers occupational medicine , urgent care , physical therapy and wellness services from more than 300 medical centers in 42 states .", "bef_words": "Privately held", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Texas", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Dell", "entity_2": "Austin", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Analysts said that <ORG>Dell</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Austin</LOC> , <LOC>Texas</LOC> , and has already introduced other <MSC>Pentium-based</MSC> computers , was trying to establish an early lead in the market so it could cash in when demand accelerated .", "bef_words": "said that", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", Texas", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "JetBlue", "entity_2": "Forest Hills", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>JetBlue</ORG> , based in <LOC>Forest Hills</LOC> , <LOC>New York</LOC> , is a five-year-old low-fare airline with 286 flights a day and destinations in 13 states and the <LOC>Caribbean</LOC> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", New", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "3Com", "entity_2": "Santa Clara", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Engineers at <ORG>3Com</ORG> , based in <LOC>Santa Clara</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , have come up with an ingenious solution to the screen cover problem : There are channels carved into both sides of the device , made to fit either the included weighted stylus or the edge of a leather and rubber cover pad . Users can decide whether they want the elegant cover pad to open on the left or right . A small detail , but nice .", "bef_words": "Engineers at", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Altadis", "entity_2": "Madrid", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Altadis</ORG> , based in <LOC>Madrid</LOC> , owns the <LOC>Fortuna</LOC> , Nobel and Fine cigarette brands , along with a range of premium cigars including <ORG>Cohiba</ORG> and <LOC>Montecristo</LOC> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", owns", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Citigroup", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Citigroup</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>New York</LOC> , on Monday announced a management shake-up apparently aimed at bolstering its cost cutting efforts .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", on", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lufthansa", "entity_2": "Cologne", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Shares of <ORG>Lufthansa</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Cologne</LOC> , were down 1 percent in <LOC>Frankfurt</LOC> trading at euro12 .16 ( $ 16.47 ) .", "bef_words": "Shares of", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", were", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Comcast", "entity_2": "Philadelphia", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "For <ORG>Comcast</ORG> , based in <LOC>Philadelphia</LOC> , and the <PER>Roberts</PER> family , which controls the company , the agreement caps four decades of deal making that began when <PER>Ralph J. Roberts</PER> sold his family 's belt business for the money to begin laying television cables .", "bef_words": "For", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", and", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "CNES", "entity_2": "Toulouse", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The <ORG>CNES</ORG> is based in <LOC>Toulouse</LOC> and would have been alerted immediately in case of a signal picked up by one of five satellites orbiting the <ORG>Earth</ORG> .", "bef_words": "The", "bet_words": "is based in", "aft_words": "and would", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Transocean", "entity_2": "Zug", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<PER>Newman</PER> said <ORG>Transocean</ORG> , based in <LOC>Zug</LOC> , <LOC>Switzerland</LOC> , has received $ 560 million in insurance proceeds for the rig .", "bef_words": "Newman said", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Switzerland", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "American Century Investments", "entity_2": "Kansas City", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>American Century Investments</ORG> , based in <LOC>Kansas City</LOC> , now has 80 employees _ about 30 percent _ of its mutual fund account service department working in their own homes .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", now", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Unification Church", "entity_2": "South Korea", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The <ORG>Unification Church</ORG> , based in <LOC>South Korea</LOC> , claims between 2 million and 3 million followers .", "bef_words": "The", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", claims", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Bre-X", "entity_2": "Ontario", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Securities regulators in both <LOC>Alberta</LOC> , where <ORG>Bre-X</ORG> is based , and <LOC>Ontario</LOC> , where the company has its main stock exchange listing , announced they were launching official investigations into allegations of fraud .", "bef_words": ", where", "bet_words": "is based , and", "aft_words": ", where", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "KeyCorp", "entity_2": "Ohio", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>KeyCorp</ORG> , based in <LOC>Ohio</LOC> , announced Wednesday a net loss of 236 million dollars in the March-June period .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", announced", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Texaco", "entity_2": "White Plains", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Texaco</ORG> , based in <LOC>White Plains</LOC> , <LOC>N.Y.</LOC> , has been seeking a way to improve its refining business for some time . Talks with <ORG>Shell</ORG> began last year , which resulted in a memorandum of understanding to form an alliance .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", N.Y.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Forrester Research", "entity_2": "Cambridge", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "`` <ORG>Yahoo</ORG> is certainly coming closer to that , '' said <PER>Henry H. Harteveldt</PER> , a travel industry analyst with <ORG>Forrester Research</ORG> , based in <LOC>Cambridge</LOC> , <LOC>Mass.</LOC> . <ORG>Google</ORG> , meanwhile , recently began offering airfare searches from its search box .", "bef_words": "analyst with", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Mass", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "National Abortion Federation", "entity_2": "Washington", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The advertisements at issue , which would have been displayed inside <LOC>Atlanta</LOC> buses , sprang from a new campaign by the <ORG>National Abortion Federation</ORG> , based in <LOC>Washington</LOC> . They were aimed in part at discouraging harassment of abortion patients and violence against abortion providers , and they have been accepted by transit systems in seven cities : <LOC>Miami</LOC> , <LOC>Washington</LOC> , <LOC>Seattle</LOC> , <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> , <ORG>Cleveland</ORG> , <LOC>Chicago</LOC> and <LOC>New York</LOC> . Only in <LOC>Atlanta</LOC> have they been turned down .", "bef_words": "by the", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ". They", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Scientific Atlanta", "entity_2": "Norcross", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Scientific Atlanta</ORG> , based in <LOC>Norcross</LOC> , <LOC>Georgia</LOC> , will provide equipment that will enable U S West to transmit video , voice and data over fiber-optic equipment . <ORG>Antec</ORG> , based in <LOC>Rolling Meadows</LOC> , <LOC>Illinois</LOC> , develops and supplies optical transmission equipment for the cable-TV industry .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Georgia", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Antec", "entity_2": "Rolling Meadows", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Scientific Atlanta</ORG> , based in <LOC>Norcross</LOC> , <LOC>Georgia</LOC> , will provide equipment that will enable U S West to transmit video , voice and data over fiber-optic equipment . <ORG>Antec</ORG> , based in <LOC>Rolling Meadows</LOC> , <LOC>Illinois</LOC> , develops and supplies optical transmission equipment for the cable-TV industry .", "bef_words": "equipment .", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Illinois", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Mystic", "entity_2": "San Diego", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The <LOC>Avalon</LOC> and its sister craft , the <ORG>Mystic</ORG> , have been based in <LOC>San Diego</LOC> for nearly 30 years but have never been needed for a rescue operation . The <LOC>United States</LOC> has lost only two nuclear-powered submarines , the Thresher and the <ORG>Scorpion</ORG> . Both sank in the 1960s in such deep waters that there was no chance of saving anyone .", "bef_words": ", the", "bet_words": ", have been based in", "aft_words": "for nearly", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lucent", "entity_2": "Murray Hill", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Camden-based <PER>Campbell</PER> shares fell 1/2 to 46 . <ORG>Lucent</ORG> , based in <LOC>Murray Hill</LOC> , saw its shares fall 3/8 to 7/8 . <ORG>Tellurian Inc.</ORG> , the maker of virtual reality products based in <LOC>Upper Saddle River</LOC> , saw its shares fall 5/8 to 1/8 . Martlon-based <ORG>MedQuist Inc.</ORG> shares fell 1/2 to 1/2 . The stock of <ORG>HFS Inc.</ORG> , the hotel franchiser and real estate broker , fell 1/2 to 1/2 .", "bef_words": "46 .", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", saw", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Informa", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Informa</ORG> , based in <LOC>London</LOC> , said this would grow to 7.6 billion dollars by 2010 .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", said", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Biomet", "entity_2": "Warsaw", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Nephew , based in <LOC>Britain</LOC> , gets more than half of its revenue from outside the <LOC>United States</LOC> . Its international distribution network could accelerate overseas sales for <ORG>Biomet</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Warsaw</LOC> , <LOC>Ind.</LOC> , while <ORG>Biomet</ORG> could extend <PER>Smith", "bef_words": "sales for", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", Ind", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "UPS Airlines", "entity_2": "Louisville", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>UPS Airlines</ORG> , based in <LOC>Louisville</LOC> , <LOC>Ky.</LOC> , is negotiating with travel companies to terminate the flights by year 's end , spokesman <PER>Mark Giuffre</PER> said Wednesday .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Ky.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Gucci", "entity_2": "Florence", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Gucci</ORG> , based in <LOC>Florence</LOC> , <LOC>Italy</LOC> , makes shoes and other leather goods . The company 's <ORG>New York</ORG> registered shares fell 9/16 in afternoon trading to 13/16 today . <ORG>Each New York</ORG> share represents one ordinary share .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Italy", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "The Antique Wine Company", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<PER>Stephen Williams</PER> , president of <ORG>The Antique Wine Company</ORG> based in <LOC>London</LOC> , was bidding for clients in major markets : the <LOC>United States</LOC> , <LOC>Japan</LOC> and <LOC>China</LOC> .", "bef_words": "president of", "bet_words": "based in", "aft_words": ", was", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Citigroup", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Citigroup</ORG> , also based in <LOC>New York</LOC> , took an after-tax charge of $ 4.95 billion , or 95 cents a share , to pay for the previously announced settlement and bolster the company 's reserves to cover further litigation .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", also based in", "aft_words": ", took", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Medtronic", "entity_2": "Minneapolis", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>St. Jude</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>St. Paul</LOC> , fell 75 cents , or 1.55 percent , to $ 47.52 a share . <ORG>Medtronic</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Minneapolis</LOC> , fell 23 cents , or 0.4 percent , to $ 56.74 a share .", "bef_words": "share .", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", fell", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "BankAmerica", "entity_2": "San Francisco", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The job cuts will eliminate about 4 per cent of the bank 's 92,700 employees . <ORG>BankAmerica</ORG> , based in <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> , also plans to close 120 of its 1,400-or-so branch offices . The company will write off $ 165 million against its fourth-quarter profit to cover the costs of the moves . And more firings and branch closings could be coming , a bank spokesman said .", "bef_words": "employees .", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", also", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Diageo", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Diageo</ORG> , based in <LOC>London</LOC> , has been trying to sell Burger King for two years in an effort to rid itself of a struggling business and focus on its core beer and liquor operation , including <ORG>Guinness</ORG> and <PER>Johnnie Walker</PER> . In July , <ORG>Diageo</ORG> announced an agreement with the buyout firms . But that deal hinged on Burger King 's meeting certain undisclosed performance goals in the fiscal year that ended in June . Burger King apparently fell short of those goals and , last month , its potential buyers pulled out .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", has", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Google", "entity_2": "Mountain View", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Google</ORG> , based in <LOC>Mountain View</LOC> , <LOC>California</LOC> , had insisted the settlement merited court approval until the <ORG>Justice Department</ORG> raised red flags .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", California", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "World Boxing Council", "entity_2": "Mexico City", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "He noted that the <ORG>World Boxing Council</ORG> , based in <LOC>Mexico City</LOC> , is boycotting bouts in <LOC>California</LOC> .", "bef_words": "that the", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", is", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NCC AB", "entity_2": "Stockholm", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>NCC AB</ORG> is based in <LOC>Stockholm</LOC> , <LOC>Sweden</LOC> , and has a 22,000-person work force worldwide .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": "is based in", "aft_words": ", Sweden", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Abendzeitung", "entity_2": "Munich", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "This is absolutely not the performance that we expected , '' <PER>Gerhard Berger</PER> , <ORG>BMW</ORG> 's outgoing motorsports director , was quoted as saying by the <ORG>Abendzeitung</ORG> , based in <LOC>Munich</LOC> , <LOC>Germany</LOC> .", "bef_words": "by the", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Germany", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Gap Inc.", "entity_2": "San Francisco", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "But businesses like <ORG>Old Navy</ORG> , which is part of <ORG>Gap Inc.</ORG> and based in <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> , and <ORG>Starbucks</ORG> , based in <LOC>Seattle</LOC> , come from a friendlier corporate culture that demands more courtesy from their stores , and the same guidelines apply from <LOC>Jefferson City</LOC> to <LOC>Jersey City</LOC> . <PER>Barnes", "bef_words": "part of", "bet_words": "and based in", "aft_words": ", and", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Starbucks", "entity_2": "Seattle", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "But businesses like <ORG>Old Navy</ORG> , which is part of <ORG>Gap Inc.</ORG> and based in <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> , and <ORG>Starbucks</ORG> , based in <LOC>Seattle</LOC> , come from a friendlier corporate culture that demands more courtesy from their stores , and the same guidelines apply from <LOC>Jefferson City</LOC> to <LOC>Jersey City</LOC> . <PER>Barnes", "bef_words": ", and", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", come", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Federal Reserve", "entity_2": "Houston", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Last year , through July , oil and gas production gave the <LOC>Houston</LOC> region 3,800 new jobs . Through July this year , the industry lost 100 jobs . Over all , the continuing expansion in retailing and construction had allowed the area to keep adding jobs at a strong pace . But <PER>Robert Gilmer</PER> , a <ORG>Federal Reserve</ORG> economist based in <LOC>Houston</LOC> , said those sectors were coasting on the energy industry 's past strength ; he predicted a slowdown for the rest of the year . Without a stronger energy business , he said , `` We ca n't survive for long by taking in each other 's laundry . ''", "bef_words": ", a", "bet_words": "economist based in", "aft_words": ", said", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Cisco", "entity_2": "San Jose", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Cisco</ORG> , based in <LOC>San Jose</LOC> , has struggled to gain shareholder approval of the deal .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", has", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Raytheon", "entity_2": "Lexington", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Raytheon</ORG> , based in <LOC>Lexington</LOC> , <LOC>Massachusetts</LOC> , said it expected to make a taxable gain on the sale .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Massachusetts", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Netscape", "entity_2": "Mountain View", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Netscape</ORG> , based in <LOC>Mountain View</LOC> , <LOC>California</LOC> , also said <ORG>Microsoft</ORG> 's announcement of 20 corporations was a drop in the bucket , compared to the 200 companies it has signed up .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", California", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Nokia", "entity_2": "Espoo", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Nokia</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Espoo</LOC> just outside <LOC>Helsinki</LOC> , has operations in 130 countries .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": "just outside", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Symantec", "entity_2": "Cupertino", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Symantec</ORG> , based in <LOC>Cupertino</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , is best known as the manufacturer of <PER>Norton</PER> AntiVirus software , which protects millions of personal computers from online attack . <ORG>Axent</ORG> of <LOC>Rockville</LOC> , Md. , creates software that defends corporate computer networks .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Internet", "entity_2": "Fort Collins", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Colorado 's Front Range Internet Inc.</ORG> , based in <LOC>Fort Collins</LOC> , went from a handful of mostly business <ORG>Internet</ORG> call customers a year ago to about 1,200 now , said <PER>Bill Ward</PER> , company president .", "bef_words": "Front Range", "bet_words": "Inc. , based in", "aft_words": ", went", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Phar-Mor", "entity_2": "Youngstown", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Phar-Mor</ORG> , based in <LOC>Youngstown</LOC> , <LOC>Ohio</LOC> , plans to establish a new holding company , <ORG>Cabot Noble Inc.</ORG> , for both companies ' discount stores as part of the acquisition .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Ohio", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Interpol", "entity_2": "France", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Interpol</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>France</LOC> , says it is determined to `` bring the murderers to justice . ''", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", says", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "OMX", "entity_2": "Stockholm", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>OMX</ORG> , based in <LOC>Stockholm</LOC> , reported on Thursday that second-quarter profit rose 53 percent .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", reported", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Phorm", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "`` Now , you can turn things around for the advertising industry , and say , ` You define the audience you want to reach , '' ' said <PER>Kent Ertugrul</PER> , chief executive of <ORG>Phorm</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>London</LOC> .", "bef_words": "executive of", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Florida Crystals", "entity_2": "Palm Beach", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "His family business , <ORG>Florida Crystals</ORG> , is based in <LOC>Palm Beach</LOC> , <LOC>Florida</LOC> .", "bef_words": "business ,", "bet_words": ", is based in", "aft_words": ", Florida", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Delta", "entity_2": "Atlanta", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The combined carrier would be called <ORG>Delta</ORG> and based in <LOC>Atlanta</LOC> , with <ORG>Delta</ORG> chief executive <PER>Richard Anderson</PER> as the chief executive at the helm .", "bef_words": "be called", "bet_words": "and based in", "aft_words": ", with", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "United Nations", "entity_2": "Geneva", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<LOC>Iran</LOC> 's embassy in <LOC>Switzerland</LOC> is in <LOC>Bern</LOC> , while a consulate and the headquarters of <LOC>Iran</LOC> 's representatives to the <ORG>United Nations</ORG> are based in <LOC>Geneva</LOC> .", "bef_words": "to the", "bet_words": "are based in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Luxottica", "entity_2": "Milan", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Luxottica</ORG> , based in <LOC>Milan</LOC> , makes sunglasses and eyeglass frames for sale worldwide .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", makes", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Suzuki", "entity_2": "Hamamatsu", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Suzuki</ORG> , based in <LOC>Hamamatsu</LOC> , is 20.1 percent owned by <ORG>General Motors Corp.</ORG> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", is", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Enron", "entity_2": "Manhattan", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "While investigators for the district attorney , <PER>Robert Morgenthau</PER> , have begun interviewing witnesses in <LOC>Houston</LOC> , where <ORG>Enron</ORG> is based , <LOC>Manhattan</LOC> prosecutors do not appear to be close to bringing any charges , people involved in the case said . There is no indication that the banks themselves are targets of the inquiry .", "bef_words": ", where", "bet_words": "is based ,", "aft_words": "prosecutors do", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Google", "entity_2": "Mountain View", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Google</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Mountain View</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , is trying to make inroads in the business through its book digitization project and book search service .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Delta Air Lines", "entity_2": "Atlanta", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Delta Air Lines</ORG> , based in <LOC>Atlanta</LOC> , led the boost this time , raising business fares $ 60 for round trips of 1,000 miles or more . Other carriers joined in over the weekend , and by Monday most companies also had raised prices by $ 20 for round trips up to 500 miles and $ 40 for round trips between 500 and 1,000 miles .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", led", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "World Economic Forum", "entity_2": "Davos", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The <ORG>World Economic Forum</ORG> , based in <LOC>Davos</LOC> , <LOC>Switzerland</LOC> , is holding its last regional meeting in <LOC>Hong Kong</LOC> before the territory returns to <MSC>Chinese</MSC> sovereignty next July 1 after more than 150 years of <MSC>British</MSC> rule .", "bef_words": "The", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Switzerland", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Better Place", "entity_2": "Palo Alto", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Such a future , experts say , might also entail auto companies transforming the way they do business , working closely with electric utilities or startups like <ORG>Better Place</ORG> , based in <LOC>Palo Alto</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , to provide cars , batteries and electricity as a bundled service with monthly fees .", "bef_words": "startups like", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Revlon", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The proposed stock sale follows an initial public offering by <ORG>Estee Lauder Cos.</ORG> , another cosmetics maker . <ORG>Revlon</ORG> , based in <LOC>New York</LOC> and owned by <PER>Ronald Perelman</PER> , is one of the best known names in cosmetics .", "bef_words": "maker .", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": "and owned", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Verisign", "entity_2": "Mountain View", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Verisign</ORG> , based in <LOC>Mountain View</LOC> , <LOC>California</LOC> , says it daily routes some 14.5 billion Internet queries to '' . com '' and '' . net '' sites and 10 million mobile phone messages and processes online purchases worth <MSC>US$</MSC> 100 million ( euro77 .74 million ) .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", California", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Napster", "entity_2": "Redwood City", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<PER>Konrad Hilbers</PER> , the chief operating officer of <ORG>Napster</ORG> , based in <LOC>Redwood City</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , called the settlement and the royalty agreement a big step toward that goal . But he also conceded that the agreement represented a substantial financial burden to <ORG>Napster</ORG> , which at present has no revenue .", "bef_words": "officer of", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Intel", "entity_2": "Santa Clara", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Intel</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Santa Clara</LOC> , is not the first major semiconductor company to commit to using 12-inch wafers . However , because <ORG>Intel</ORG> sets the pace for the industry , its decision is certain to force other chip makers to move to next-generation chip fabrication .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", is", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lucent", "entity_2": "Murray Hill", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Lucent</ORG> said the job cuts would be in the <LOC>United States</LOC> as well as in other countries . <ORG>Lucent</ORG> , which is based in <LOC>Murray Hill</LOC> , <LOC>N.J.</LOC> , employs about 8,400 people in <LOC>New Jersey</LOC> .", "bef_words": "countries .", "bet_words": ", which is based in", "aft_words": ", N.J.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NASCAR", "entity_2": "Daytona Beach", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Until last week , the project , which could cost up to $ 600 million in private funds and take until 2010 to be completed , seemed to be inching forward . In May 2004 , officials of the <ORG>International Speedway Corporation</ORG> , a <ORG>NASCAR</ORG> affiliate based in <LOC>Daytona Beach</LOC> , <LOC>Fla.</LOC> , confirmed their plans to build the race track . That December , they paid $ 100 million to buy 450 of the roughly 660 acres of the site , an abandoned petroleum tank farm near the <LOC>Goethals Bridge</LOC> . -LRB- A developer plans to build a shopping center on the remaining land . -RRB-", "bef_words": ", a", "bet_words": "affiliate based in", "aft_words": ", Fla.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lashkar-e-Taiba", "entity_2": "Kashmir", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<PER>Kasab</PER> said he and the other gunmen were `` hand-picked '' for the mission and trained for more than a year by <ORG>Lashkar-e-Taiba</ORG> , based in <LOC>Kashmir</LOC> , according to two senior officials involved in the investigation .", "bef_words": "year by", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", according", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Wachovia", "entity_2": "Charlotte", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "Even the state 's banking industry is on edge . The recent merger of <ORG>Wachovia</ORG> , based in <LOC>Charlotte</LOC> , with <PER>Wells Fargo</PER> has created great uncertainty , with possible layoffs in the offing .", "bef_words": "merger of", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", with", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Entergy", "entity_2": "New Orleans", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "The five-member commission voted unanimously to transfer the operating license of the plant to <ORG>Entergy</ORG> , based in <LOC>New Orleans</LOC> , from <LOC>Con Edison</LOC> , which must sell its electric power plants under a state plan to create a competitive electricity market .", "bef_words": "plant to", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", from", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Google", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "`` We were not able to make our case directly to the judge , '' said <PER>David Collins</PER> , a spokesman for <ORG>Google</ORG> based in <LOC>London</LOC> . `` We are disappointed by the decision , which we believe is flawed and which we intend to appeal . ''", "bef_words": "spokesman for", "bet_words": "based in", "aft_words": ". ``", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Stanford", "entity_2": "Caribbean", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "For the past two decades , <ORG>Stanford</ORG> has been based in the <LOC>Caribbean</LOC> , where he built a reputation as a cricket patron .", "bef_words": "decades ,", "bet_words": "has been based in the", "aft_words": ", where", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Newsday", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "In the six months that ended Sept. 30 , <ORG>The Los Angeles Times</ORG> reported a 4.7 percent decline in daily circulation , to slightly more than 1 million . <ORG>Newsday</ORG> , which is based on <LOC>New York</LOC> 's <LOC>Long Island</LOC> , reported an 8.5 percent drop in circulation , to 634,627 .", "bef_words": "million .", "bet_words": ", which is based on", "aft_words": "'s Long", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Lycos", "entity_2": "Waltham", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Lycos</ORG> , based in <LOC>Waltham</LOC> , <LOC>Mass.</LOC> , saw its stock rise 5/16 to 1/16 on the <MSC>Nasdaq</MSC> stock exchange Tuesday .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", Mass", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Wachovia", "entity_2": "Charlotte", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Wachovia</ORG> , based in <LOC>Charlotte</LOC> , expects the deal to be neutral to its 2007 net income .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", expects", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Oxford", "entity_2": "Toronto", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>Oxford</ORG> , based in <LOC>Toronto</LOC> , has stakes in 21 million square feet of real estate and manages 45 million square feet for others . <ORG>GE Capital Canada</ORG> is part of the financial services unit of <ORG>General Electric Co.</ORG> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", has", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NationsBank", "entity_2": "Charlotte", "confidence": 0.9877300613496932, "sentence": "<ORG>NationsBank</ORG> , based in <LOC>Charlotte</LOC> , <LOC>North Carolina</LOC> will join the e-check test during the second quarter , according to <PER>Stephen Schutze</PER> , a <ORG>NationsBank</ORG> senior vice president in charge of transaction services strategic planning .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based in", "aft_words": ", North", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Avondale", "entity_2": "New Orleans", "confidence": 0.8312894963470859, "sentence": "If <ORG>Avondale</ORG> , which is based near <LOC>New Orleans</LOC> , does agree to be acquired by <ORG>Litton</ORG> , this could put more pressure on <ORG>Newport News</ORG> to accept the deal as well , since <ORG>Newport News</ORG> would lose its own opportunity to grow by acquiring <ORG>Avondale</ORG> . <ORG>Litton</ORG> has said either acquisition could go ahead without the other .", "bef_words": "If", "bet_words": ", which is based near", "aft_words": ", does", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "MSNBC", "entity_2": "Manhattan", "confidence": 0.8312894963470859, "sentence": "<ORG>MSNBC</ORG> , based near <LOC>Manhattan</LOC> in northern <LOC>New Jersey</LOC> , will debut in 22 million houomes with cable hookups , about one third the number of homes that are receiving <ORG>CNN</ORG> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", based near", "aft_words": "in northern", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Reliance", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "Reliance , headquartered in <LOC>New York</LOC> , with 3,000 employees , reported an operating loss of $ 318.3 million last year , and $ 36.5 million in this year 's first quarter . Recent blows included a major setback in a workers ' compensation insurance arrangement that went sour . Steinberg stepped down as chief executive in late February , on the day <ORG>Reliance</ORG> announced the sale of its profitable `` crown jewel , '' a surety unit , for $ 580 million .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", headquartered in", "aft_words": ", with", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "DoubleClick", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "<ORG>DoubleClick</ORG> , headquartered in <LOC>New York</LOC> , announced an acquisition agreement on Sunday which is expected to be completed in the third quarter .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", headquartered in", "aft_words": ", announced", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Wachovia", "entity_2": "Charlotte", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "<ORG>Wachovia</ORG> is headquartered in <LOC>Charlotte</LOC> , <LOC>North Carolina</LOC> .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": "is headquartered in", "aft_words": ", North", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Delphi", "entity_2": "Troy", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "The spinoff left <ORG>Delphi</ORG> , which generated $ 28.5 billion in revenue last year , as the world 's 25th largest company and transformed the <LOC>Dayton</LOC> area from a GM to a <ORG>Delphi</ORG> stronghold . <ORG>Delphi</ORG> , headquartered in <LOC>Troy</LOC> , <LOC>Mich.</LOC> , has 200,000 employees and operates 169 plants worldwide .", "bef_words": "stronghold .", "bet_words": ", headquartered in", "aft_words": ", Mich.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "SAP", "entity_2": "Walldorf", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "<ORG>SAP</ORG> , headquartered in <LOC>Walldorf</LOC> , <LOC>Germany</LOC> , says the acquisition will also give it key technology from <ORG>Sybase</ORG> that lets business programs run on mobile phones .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", headquartered in", "aft_words": ", Germany", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Peapod", "entity_2": "Chicago", "confidence": 0.33333333333333326, "sentence": "<ORG>Peapod</ORG> , headquartered in <LOC>Chicago</LOC> , now says it is profitable in all the markets it serves , but it does n't face competition from a large company like <ORG>Albertsons</ORG> . <ORG>Peapod</ORG> said the company has been expecting <ORG>Albertsons</ORG> to launch in several markets it serves .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": ", headquartered in", "aft_words": ", now", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Intralot", "entity_2": "Bulgaria", "confidence": 0.23124525944391883, "sentence": "Apart from <LOC>Greece</LOC> , <ORG>Intralot</ORG> already operates in <LOC>Bulgaria</LOC> , <LOC>Moldova</LOC> and <LOC>Romania</LOC> , and has received deals to begin operations in <LOC>Chile</LOC> and <LOC>Peru</LOC> .", "bef_words": "Greece ,", "bet_words": "already operates in", "aft_words": ", Moldova", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Exelon", "entity_2": "Illinois", "confidence": 0.23124525944391883, "sentence": "<ORG>Exelon</ORG> operates 17 reactors in <LOC>Illinois</LOC> , <LOC>Pennsylvania</LOC> and <LOC>New Jersey</LOC> . Many of those units are on large tracts of land that could accommodate another reactor .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": "operates 17 reactors in", "aft_words": ", Pennsylvania", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Europe", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "After brief talks with the speakers of <LOC>Belgium</LOC> 's two houses of parliament , he will later visit <ORG>NATO</ORG> 's military headquarters in <LOC>Europe</LOC> at <LOC>Mons</LOC> , south of <LOC>Brussels</LOC> .", "bef_words": "later visit", "bet_words": "'s military headquarters in", "aft_words": "at Mons", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Genentech", "entity_2": "South San Francisco", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "Those operations will be based at <ORG>Genentech</ORG> 's headquarters in <LOC>South San Francisco</LOC> , <LOC>California</LOC> .", "bef_words": "based at", "bet_words": "'s headquarters in", "aft_words": ", California", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "US Airways", "entity_2": "Arlington", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "The airline closed out 2001 with a failed merger , rocky labor relations , a slumping stock price , and a $ 2 billion loss that accounted for more than a quarter of the annual losses posted by the nation 's top seven carriers . When air traffic plummeted after Sept. 11 , executives at <ORG>US Airways</ORG> ' headquarters in <LOC>Arlington</LOC> , <LOC>Va.</LOC> , announced the elimination of 11,000 positions and slashed more than 20 percent of flight service .", "bef_words": "executives at", "bet_words": "' headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Va.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Philips", "entity_2": "Eindhoven", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "Speaking at a press conference at <ORG>Philips</ORG> ' headquarters in <LOC>Eindhoven</LOC> , the <LOC>Netherlands</LOC> , <PER>Dudley Eustace</PER> , <ORG>Philips</ORG> executive vice president and board member , said both <ORG>PKI</ORG> and TRT were making losses and that discussions about the partial sale had been going on for some time .", "bef_words": "conference at", "bet_words": "' headquarters in", "aft_words": ", the", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "World Bank", "entity_2": "Washington", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "The meeting was at the <ORG>World Bank</ORG> 's headquarters in <LOC>Washington</LOC> .", "bef_words": "at the", "bet_words": "'s headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "<ORG>NATO</ORG> 's final assessment will be announced Monday by Gen. <PER>George Joulwan</PER> in <ORG>NATO</ORG> 's headquarters , <LOC>Brussels</LOC> .", "bef_words": "Joulwan in", "bet_words": "'s headquarters ,", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Interpol", "entity_2": "Lyon", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "It urged anyone with knowledge of her whereabouts to contact their local police or <ORG>Interpol</ORG> 's headquarters in <LOC>Lyon</LOC> , <LOC>France</LOC> .", "bef_words": "police or", "bet_words": "'s headquarters in", "aft_words": ", France", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Moxi", "entity_2": "Palo Alto", "confidence": 0.21593009427684628, "sentence": "In an interview last week at <ORG>Moxi</ORG> 's headquarters in <LOC>Palo Alto</LOC> , <LOC>Calif.</LOC> , <PER>Perlman</PER> said he had embarked on his current course after spending almost $ 1 million to build a custom system with similar features at his vacation home in <LOC>Tahoe</LOC> .", "bef_words": "week at", "bet_words": "'s headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Calif.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NASA", "entity_2": "Washington", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "Around 19,000 employees work at <ORG>NASA</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Washington</LOC> and in its 10 command centers around the <LOC>United States</LOC> , along with an additional 40,000 contractors to the space agency .", "bef_words": "work at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "and in", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Nintendo", "entity_2": "Kyoto", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "<PER>Miyamoto</PER> , 49 , may be unknown to many , but hardcore gaming fans revere him as an icon _ a man who has created a multitude of memorable video game titles working quietly from <ORG>Nintendo</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Kyoto</LOC> , <LOC>Japan</LOC> .", "bef_words": "quietly from", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Japan", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Cerner", "entity_2": "North Kansas City", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "R Block headquarters project now under construction downtown and 3.16 million for the expansion of the <ORG>Cerner</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>North Kansas City</LOC> . Both projects are being assisted by the state BUILD program .", "bef_words": "of the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ". Both", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "Officials at <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> said the alliance has been putting the final touches on a number of options , but these plans were nothing new .", "bef_words": "Officials at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "said the", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Central Election Commission", "entity_2": "Taipei", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "The protest comes a day after about 2,000 people stormed the <ORG>Central Election Commission</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Taipei</LOC> .", "bef_words": "stormed the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "UEFA", "entity_2": "Switzerland", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "That appeal was backed by the <ORG>Football Association</ORG> , but the indications from <ORG>UEFA</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Switzerland</LOC> were that it would fall on deaf ears .", "bef_words": "indications from", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "were that", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "London", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "Their trip will wrap up in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> for discussions at <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters and then <LOC>London</LOC> around December 8 , a key deadline for <LOC>Iraq</LOC> to submit a report on its weapons programs to the <ORG>United Nations</ORG> , the official said .", "bef_words": "discussions at", "bet_words": "headquarters and then", "aft_words": "around December", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "PDVSA", "entity_2": "Caracas", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "A march to the <ORG>PDVSA</ORG> headquarters in central <LOC>Caracas</LOC> was stopped by opposition leaders saying they feared clashes with presidential supporters .", "bef_words": "to the", "bet_words": "headquarters in central", "aft_words": "was stopped", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "<ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> said the soldiers did not fire their weapons during the arrest attempt .", "bef_words": "", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "said the", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "UNESCO", "entity_2": "Paris", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "The <ORG>World Digital Library</ORG> , a website offering free access to rare books , maps , manuscripts , films and photographs from across the globe , will launch April 21 at <ORG>UNESCO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Paris</LOC> .", "bef_words": "21 at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Securities and Exchange Commission", "entity_2": "Washington", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "For the past 20 years , <PER>Fisher</PER> led the firm 's financial and asset management operations , helping the company broker deals that included the acquisition of a 9-acre parcel south of the <ORG>United Nations</ORG> , one of the city 's largest available development sites , and the expansion of the <ORG>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Washington</LOC> .", "bef_words": "of the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "OPEC", "entity_2": "Vienna", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "<ORG>OPEC</ORG> has n't received formal notification yet from <LOC>Iraq</LOC> about its embargo , and it was still unclear whether <LOC>Iraq</LOC> planned to halt all of its shipments , the source said , speaking on condition of anonymity from <ORG>OPEC</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Vienna</LOC> , <LOC>Austria</LOC> .", "bef_words": "anonymity from", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Austria", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "There was no immediate reponse from <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> , where an official said the 19 alliance ambassadors had a general discussion of the proposal , describing it as being in early stages .", "bef_words": "reponse from", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", where", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "`` I commend the <MSC>Afghan</MSC> security forces for the role they have played in defending against these attacks and restoring order in the city , '' he said in a statement from <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> .", "bef_words": "statement from", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "`` It 's looked upon by the <LOC>US</LOC> government as a very , very serious situation , '' he said during a visit to <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> .", "bef_words": "visit to", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "United Nations", "entity_2": "New York", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "<PER>Akashi</PER> , a <MSC>Japanese</MSC> national , told a press conference at the <ORG>United Nations</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>New York</LOC> that a considerable degree of violation has taken place concerning the accord .", "bef_words": "at the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "that a", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NEC", "entity_2": "Japan", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "He also said he plans to fly to <ORG>NEC</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Japan</LOC> for discussions .", "bef_words": "fly to", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "for discussions", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Pemex", "entity_2": "Mexico City", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "In an interview at <ORG>Pemex</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Mexico City</LOC> , <PER>Antonio Sacristan Roy</PER> , the senior executive in charge of the privatization , said the government decided to sell the plants to raise new investment capital for <ORG>Pemex</ORG> 's core business : finding , pumping , refining and distributing oil and natural gas .", "bef_words": "interview at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Antonio", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Middlesex", "entity_2": "Billerica", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "The inspector general 's report , obtained by <ORG>The Globe</ORG> , chronicles the use of `` fabricated '' bids to ensure that the reconstruction of the <ORG>Middlesex</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Billerica</LOC> went to a <LOC>Westford</LOC> contractor close to two board members . `` The board 's actions in this matter represent a profound breach of public trust and a misuse of beneficiaries ' money , '' Inspector General <PER>Gregory W. Sullivan</PER> said in an 11-page letter to the <ORG>Public Employee Retirement Administration Commission</ORG> , or <ORG>PERAC</ORG> , which oversees the state 's 106 public pension systems .", "bef_words": "of the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "went to", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "PepsiCo", "entity_2": "Purchase", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "He will be remembered in a private ceremony and at a tribute in September at <ORG>PepsiCo</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Purchase</LOC> , <LOC>New York</LOC> .", "bef_words": "September at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", New", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Fiat", "entity_2": "Turin", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "Born into a family of upper-middle-class communists , <PER>Ferrara</PER> spent part of his childhood in <LOC>Moscow</LOC> , where his father was a correspondent for the communist daily <ORG>L'Unita</ORG> . In his 20s , he was the chief organizer for the <ORG>Italian Communist Party</ORG> at the <ORG>Fiat</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Turin</LOC> , when labor relations were tense and the <ORG>Red Brigades</ORG> were unsettling the country . But <PER>Ferrara</PER> soured on the communist hardliners , and in 1982 left the party entirely , becoming its most vocal apostate . He grew enamored of the political philosopher <PER>Leo Strauss</PER> , who wrote of the tensions between <LOC>Athens</LOC> and <LOC>Jerusalem</LOC> , reason and faith .", "bef_words": "at the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", when", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "United Nations", "entity_2": "Baghdad", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "A <MSC>Spanish</MSC> navy captain was killed in the truck bombing of the <ORG>United Nations</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Baghdad</LOC> on Aug. 19 .", "bef_words": "of the", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "on Aug.", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "Interpol", "entity_2": "Paris", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "`` Four countries have confirmed the presence of five absconders although we have traced four more absconders in three other countries , '' he told reporters on his return from a 10-day visit to <ORG>Interpol</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Paris</LOC> and <LOC>London</LOC> .", "bef_words": "visit to", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": "and London", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Brussels", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "<PER>Powell</PER> said during a visit to <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Brussels</LOC> , <LOC>Belgium</LOC> , that `` not a single member '' of the <LOC>Atlantic</LOC> alliance spoke out against taking on more responsibilities in <LOC>Iraq</LOC> .", "bef_words": "visit to", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ", Belgium", "passive_voice": false}
{"entity_1": "NATO", "entity_2": "Kabul", "confidence": 0.2159300843874613, "sentence": "In the past 90 days , 293 insurgent leaders have been captured or killed , and the <ORG>Taliban</ORG> are finding it increasingly difficult to replace commanders , according to a senior operations adviser at <ORG>NATO</ORG> headquarters in <LOC>Kabul</LOC> .", "bef_words": "adviser at", "bet_words": "headquarters in", "aft_words": ".", "passive_voice": false}
